{"trivia":[
	{"id":1,
	"question":"What is the most commonly used element in computers today?",
	"radio1": "Halfium",
	"radio2": "Nuclear isomer",
	"radio3": "Zircon",
  	"answer": "Halfium",
  	"useranswer": ""},

	{"id":2,
	"question":"What company is the largest producer of computer software for the personal computer?",
	"radio1": "Dell",
	"radio2": "Microsoft",
	"radio3": "Google",
  	"answer": "Microsoft",
  	"useranswer": ""},

	{"id":3,
	"question":"What name is given to half of a Byte (4 bits)?",
	"radio1": "Bit",
	"radio2": "Byte",
	"radio3": "Nibble",
  	"answer": "Nibble",
  	"useranswer": ""},

	{"id":4,
	"question":"What do the initials GUI stand for?",
	"radio1": "Graphical User Interaction",
	"radio2": "Graphical User Interface",
	"radio3": "Global User Interface",
  	"answer": "Graphical User Interface",
  	"useranswer": ""},
	
	{"id":5,
	"question":"From the computer world: What does the word "modem" abbreviate?",
	"radio1": "Modulation",
	"radio2": "Modulation and Demodulation",
	"radio3": "Demodulation",
  	"answer": "Modulation and Demodulation",
  	"useranswer": ""},
	
	{"id":6,
	"question":"If the telephone company added one more digit to all the phone numbers in one area code, how many new phone numbers could potentially be added?",
	"radio1": "90,000,000",
	"radio2": "30,000",
	"radio3": "50,000",
  	"answer": "90,000,000",
  	"useranswer": ""},

	{"id":7,
	"question":"Where do flies go in the winter? Do they die, fly to warmer climates, or hibernate?",
	"radio1": "Migrate",
	"radio2": "Hibernate",
	"radio3": "Die",
  	"answer": "Hibernate",
  	"useranswer": ""},

	{"id":8,
	"question":"What slithering animal is named for the sound that it makes before striking?",
	"radio1": "Cobra",
	"radio2": "Rattlesnake",
	"radio3": "Vipers",
  	"answer": "Rattlesnake",
  	"useranswer": ""},
	
	{"id":9,
	"question":"What type of wool comes from soft-haired llamas in Peru?",
	"radio1": "Camelidae",
	"radio2": "Alpaca",
	"radio3": "Vicugnas",
  	"answer": "Alpaca",
  	"useranswer": ""},

	{"id":10,
	"question":"What is the first animal listed in the dictionary?",
	"radio1": "Anteater",
	"radio2": "Aardvark",
	"radio3": "Armadillo",
  	"answer": "Aardvark",
  	"useranswer": ""}

]}